Jhal
Hello Hello Friends Welcome to your
own YouTube channel Investment in
Alok Industries. The much awaited quarter one results of Alok Industries are going to come tomorrow.
Friends, in today's
video we are going to tell you
how the quarterly results of Alok Industries can be and in the short term
and long term, what is the reason due to which
Alok Industries can become a
big issue. Friends, on Glass
Tuesday we had posted a video in
which we had advised you to like two shares for
friends and
also for those who are stuck at the higher rates, Alok
Industries and Yes Bank. At that time the rate of Alok Industries was
running around Rs 27 and Yes
Bank around Rs 10.50, both started and
showed a good movement from there.
Then in Alok Industries, friends, we have seen
that when this stop moves, the circuit
gives a circuit moment. Whenever a big move
comes in it, that circuit circuit comes. St.
Kitts is rapid typing at 5, the volume is high, the
flight mode circuit circuit comes due to which the
investors who are stuck at the higher rates and
also the money which is entering
Those who want to enter are unable to do so when
this top moves. This is the reason why last week
we told you that the stock is
trading near support at a very good demand level
and you should buy it for a new entry as well as on
averaging. This
could be a big issue in the coming times.
Friends, tomorrow the results of the company's famous withdrawal are
coming. Today we are going to share with you a lot of
those experiments due to which
it could face a big blow in the coming times. The
results of front part one will
come and they will be much better than the last few results. The
reason for this is that the
most awaited review of the P kit here will
repeat in the quarter
because they started making the page right from the beginning of April.
In April to June, the company has had a huge water flow of Happy Packet for 3 months, which will be
repeated in Shri Bhanu Patwan.
Apart from this, the lockdown has also been imposed since around May, so it should
also come in doing core business. We are roughly assuming that
their sales in the last quarter  It is
only around 80 crores that their
shell tomorrow can come around 900 to 1000 crores
that the revenue of PPP trend 95
masks can
come around 6.5 crores, so
including getting awards, it is possible that the
company may perform very well on the reminder front, secondly, there has been a huge
consolidation in the stock of Reddy,
this stock has shown a huge consolidation for a long time, since many
trading sessions, when I am roaming,
friends, earlier Stark applied circuit,
so the circuit should be above, in such a situation, those who
wanted to buy should be able to buy and those who
wanted to sell should be able to sit, but now assume
that after such a big consolidation, all the weak
hands or suggestions who were
looking for profit booking have come out
in the stock, now the momentum in the stock is
from Major Ali strong end and
those who have taken it by making a long time,
they are in strong, now the end vested in the stock is
27 28, in its range, Stark has
made a very strong base,
we last saw it, then a 55  By making Rs 56, a
lower circuit was applied from here, so that
stock also revolved around Rs 27 exactly from here,
then it
settled at Rs 40 ballistic research,
after that correction was seen again, this
time exactly the stock turned from there, so it has
become a big support staff,
friends, another big trigger is that there is the
Chhote Kunwar process, that is, the one which has
become Aunty, New York University, the
takeover process there has
almost been completed, hence
last week practice to has also informed
that there was equity allotment to Reliance, the
company has done it, so going forward coriander
powder is Reliance, its
addition C, the performance of the company will be seen in terms of the company's
quarterly results and new developments,
which
can take the stock forward,
friends, what kind of revenue comes in the click result,
what kind of money comes, the
market will closely master that
because in all the recent ones, the
result of many adjustments single should be
quite good on the Mirwaiz front,
which  The market is very thick for pimples,
subscribe it is already running well, there is
full chance of blood on the road, you can
see something else in the coming subscribe,
many people were asking cutter and let me
tell you that if you subscribe then
subscribe above, apart from this I can give a look, I will
tell you in Wikipedia, you stay tuned to
our channel, in this, pimples with investment
and any of your virgin, whether it is about stopping it
or your device regarding medal system, you
can tell me in the comment section, Vishal, get back to you, if
you have not subscribed to my channel,
first of all subscribe to the channel,
make the most accurate stock according to every thing, to hide it